Well look I think
we were I was
always very confident we
would get back to
sort the top of
the leaderboards and the
SOTA type of across
the because I think
we've always had the
deepest and broadest research
bench and it was
about kind marshalling that
all together and getting
the intensity and focus
and the kind start
up mentality back to
the whole organisation And
it's been a lot
of work but I
think we're still a
of to do but
I think you can
start seeing the
kind of The progress
that's been made in
both the with Gemini
3 but also on
the product side with
Gemini app getting increasing
market share So I
feel like we're making
great progress but there's
a tonne more work
to do and you
know we're bringing to
bear Google DeepMind's kind
of like the engine
room of where we're
getting used to our
more and quickly into
the product surfaces